Basically, the main things we do are
Increase funds while selling New Year's cards for 500 yen at the Gang Parade
A game of increasing the military fund to go to zero long stay art of Houkagami
After that, if you arrive at the first place, you get a 30,000 yen bonus.
25,000 yen bonus if you arrive at the second place
If you arrive in third place, you get a 20,000 yen bonus, and so on.
Each of these bonuses is based on the time of arrival.
And then there's Hanae Monster!
Hanae Monster, please!
There was a Hanae Monster in the blink of an eye until yesterday
Wait a minute.
Which one is it?
Thank you all for coming, Young Pile!
I thought I'd make a round-trip New Year's card
Between the 2nd and 3rd, we'll be scattered all over the country and our members will be selling them
In other words, we're going to go for Nakano Heavy Chic Zero.
If the members split into six teams, we'll head there.
Let's decide on the location first
Sagawa's telegram out.
I saw them running.
Have one representative from each team come up.
Yonas army team
Osaka
Tokyo
Nagoya
Wait!
Hatena!
Sembai bar!
Seino!
FUKUHANA!
Hattener!
Sorry!
It's HATENA!
Shikoku!
Again!
Kochi Prefecture!
First time!
I'm OK with borrowing money from people I know.
Borrow money?
I'm willing to borrow money from an acquaintance.
Your parents are so strong!
Then don't do that anymore.
Then don't be like that anymore.
You want to go to Vachi?
We don't have time for this.
We need to set a goal.
Our strategy meeting...
I want to call everyone we know in Osaka.
Do you think the geeks will come to Sendai on January 23rd?
Well, we could try to go to a live show or something.
Well, yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to do Eevee's... well, some kind of first sale...
Here it comes!
Wait, twice!
And it's gorgeous! And they're gorgeous!
The second one was so gorgeous!
They're so gorgeous!
These are the girls my friend choreographed!
Oh my God! They're here!
Mr. Eye Spy?
Yeah. Ask if you can put me on the tiki staff or something.
Hello. Hey, Hina. Hey, Ice Pie.
You're the choreographer.
I'm going to Sendai for a project and I need to make some money on the spot.
I was wondering if you could get me a part-time job there.
I'd be happy to put you in touch with a manager or something.
Thanks.
You mean any kind of part-time job in advance?
I can babysit if you make an appointment in advance.
Oh, great.
Is that a possibility?
Yes.
Really?
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah.
Mane Pachinko and Aichi Prefecture.
It's famous.
I've never played it.
I've never played pachinko.
Then horse racing
Yes, one on three.
At our school.
Graduates of our school...
They all get together.
So I'll make it one.
It might be a good idea to go to Tokyo
I might be able to go to Tokyo
Sell out at the end.
It's not very cost-effective to just go this way.
Sell out in a big chunk.
Gather up the money and go to the horse races
It's the simplest way to buy more
It's the simplest
Because it's the simplest way.
To be honest, Tokyo is
If you sell all your money
Selling all over the place
you can win.
Conversely, if you really want to win
If you really want to win, then Tokyo and
Osaka and Nagoya.
I think you'll have to stay in Tokyo, Osaka, and Nagoya.
To be honest...
Coach Fukuoka is fine.
It's Oita.
That's a crime.
We'll have to decide how to get home.
I guess so.
Where to go?
Leona, do you know how long it takes to get to Tokyo from Tokushima by ferry? I mean...
Hello, Leona.
Hello?
Excuse me.
I'll call you back.
Yes?
I want to go back to Tokyo from Kochi.
What do you think is the fastest way?
Out of Shikoku.
From Shikoku.
No plane?
I can only spend 30,000 yen.
Thank you, Leona.
Sorry to drop in on you like this.
Thank you.
What's in Takamatsu?
What do you do?
What the fuck?
Uber Eats
Uber Eats.
Pitch Hike.
Last group.
I think I'll go with Leona Empizer's management.
Pitch Hike...
Pitch Hike
Pitch hiking...
I don't want to.
Once we get to Okayama
I'll think of a route to Okayama
That's where we're going.
You want to go straight home from Okayama?
Or go through Osaka or something.
Or do you go directly from Okayama?
Honestly, it depends on how much money we can make.
Yes, it depends on how much money we can make.
Then...
Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh.
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
Fukuoka to Tokyo
How much will it cost?
When Mr. Takahashi arrives...
Wouldn't it be bad if it's already booked?
So he moved to Osaka.
That's right.
From Osaka.
Then we'll only see 30,000... but we'll see.
Bring lots of rice balls and stuff.
I'm just pretending... in Fukuoka...
I'm not going to give up on it, but it's like a journey...
I think it's very risky though.
I'll wait and see if there's anyone who'll put it up in the first place, and then I'll meet you in Tokyo on my own, in a bathing suit.
I'll meet you in a bathing suit!
That's too much.
Boo boo!
You're already thinking of flying home, right?
I'll just have to fly somewhere in the middle of it, like Hiroshima, and then I can come back to Tokyo.
But I was going to go to another event.
I'll do it!
Hold him down.
If he's born, he'll be profitable, right?
That's fine.
Score some points for me.
Who's going to take the checkered flag?
Let's make it a chameleon buy... a chameleon buy.
Let's do it.
I know I'm not supposed to do that.
What's a drummer?
I think he's a part-timer.
I'm available. Take a look.
I'm a drummer. I can rent you a drummer.
Take your guitar.
I'm full.
Ask Mr. Gonchuk.
I'll ask Mr. Gonchuk to take you to the idol's Chiquista.
It's better than going undercover.
If only we had some comedians
If we had comedians who knew the gamepare
It's totally different.
Miki on the 2nd.
Einstein.
Milkboy.
The Mitrys... they're going to be there.
I think it's going to be really crowded.
I'm going to be at the Gyanparee, and I'm going to say
"I'm an idol.
Someday.
You should at least have a business card.
Like a self-introduction card.
Shall we make some?
I'll print it out.
Make it.
Power Point.
I'm good at PowerPoint.
Make one and use Einstein.
Because I think it's better on one.
It's a good use of my time.
Seriously.
I'm just trying to figure out how to get around more efficiently
I'm trying to get where I'm going.
Write it down.
Write it down in a notebook or something.
Or take it with you.
Like a lube.
You don't have to do that.
You didn't say anything about it.
It's a way to make money.
Go to sleep.
It's better if it's not random.
Thank you for watching.
Tokyo's a big city, so if you're on the wrong side of town...
If it's too far off the beaten path, it's a lot of work.
You're going to have to go to the best places along the way.
Stay at a very cheap hotel or a business hotel.
Or if you're selling a lot of New Year's cards, you can stay at a nice hotel.
But you're going to run out of money, and you're going to come in first place, and you're going to get 30,000.
I honestly don't think they'd come to that.
It's too expensive to travel.
And I want to eat yakiniku.
Then what's the goal?
I want to eat grilled meat and sushi for dinner.
You dye your hair God's hair?
Let's all dye our hair God's hair.
Is it possible to have a friend treat us?
Is that possible?
For example, a kind old lady we met at the restaurant.
She treats us to a meal.
Is it dramatic like that?
So, victory, we can manage.
We'll manage.
You know, my heart will not be broken.
No matter what happens.
So, I'll bring furikake.
I'll have onigiri.
Worst case scenario, if I can find some Chingo Fun at the convenience store...
But, you know, whoever bought it.
How about some Atmode?
Oh, sure.
I'm an idol of good luck.
Well, you should go to the shrine and get out a good luck charm.
And I was thinking of buying a stimulant.
Can't you hold it?
I can't.
Awakening Apparatus.
You want to wait for us to buy it?
Yeah, we'll buy it.
One more thing.
13 hours ago gave
Maybe.
I don't know.
There are still aftershocks in some areas.
It wasn't realistic to do it under such circumstances.
But it's still frustrating.
It's frustrating.
I'm frustrated because I don't know if there will be any customers that we haven't met yet.
that Gang Parade Group was coming to Kochi.
So I thought it would be great if we could go and meet them.
I think it was a key part of this project that we were able to create an opportunity
I think that was the key to this project.
I think it was important for us to be able to go and meet those customers.
The customers we wanted to meet
I'm disappointed to think that there must have been people I could have met
I feel frustrated when I think that there must have been people I could have met
I really have to work hard this year to see them again.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you for watching!
Wow, I wrote so many role-playing videos!
Wow!
I really didn't think I should write so many role-playing videos!
I know, right?
It's a lot of work!
What are you going to do with all this?
You're right...
I wrote so many role-playing videos that I could put them all over the wall.
I was originally going to hand them out to all the people who came to the heavy ships.
That's right.
That's right, but I can't see you this time...
I don't want to change the plan, but I'd like to present the first calligraphy to all the playmates this time!
Oh!
That's nice!
But you know... when I say present...
I'm talking about the gang parade.
I was wondering if I could put it on something.
You're not going to sell it for 10,000 yen or something?
What kind of image?
Not a good image.
Maybe give it away as a bonus for pre-ordering a CD.
That's what I've heard.
Maybe it's good.
That's for sure.
Well, you know, normally I'd give it away, but it's New Year's, and it's DeLee's, and it's the holidays, and it's a free gift!
This time, we're giving it away for free to those who apply!
Free!
Seriously?
Really?
Free? Free?
Free.
Free?
And then some more.
Even more?
Not only the first calligraphy of the year, but also the New Year's greeting cards that we were going to sell in this project?
Yes, yes, yes.
Ours.
Maybe not many.
Yes, the gang parade New Year's card.
We're giving them away as a set too!
Yay!
That means the first calligraphy and the New Year's card are the New Year's gift
the New Year's gift for all the playmates!
Oh, how nice!
For more details on how to apply, please check the official Gang Parade website and SNS!
Yes, please!
I'm sorry I won't be able to see my fans from all over the country this time, but I'm sure I'll see you again soon.
I'm sure I'll see you all again soon, so please just wait a little bit longer!
Congratulations!
I miss you!
I miss you so much!
I'm going this way!
That's all for us
ENJOY PLAY Everybody Dance Weaver Gang Parade!